Film Stills and the History of Photography Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
Film Stills and the History of Photography Slide Collection
1960-2005
VRC 1450
Yale University Arts Library
15
87 boxes in 15 containers
Collection consists of color and black and white 35 mm slides of international film stills and examples from the history of photography from 1839 to the present. Film stills largely from the Museum of Modern Art film still series.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
Collection consists of color and black and white 35 mm slides of international film stills and examples from the history of photography from 1839 to the present. Film stills largely from the Museum of Modern Art film still series.
Arrangement
Arranged by country. Film stills sub-divided by film title. History of photography slides sub-divided by photographer.
Photography -- History; Motion pictures -- History; Slides; Reproductions
- Films (Box 1)
  - General (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous works [Slide box 1] (Box 1)
    - Equipment (Box 1)
    - History (Box 1)
      - Miscellaneous works (Box 1)
      - Film History: Edison (Box 1)
      - Film History: Lumiere (Box 1)
      - Film History: Magic Lantern (Box 1)
      - Film History: Shadow Plays (Box 1)
      - Film History: Plays (Box 1)
    - Production [Slide boxes 1-2] (Box 1)
  - Britain (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous works (Box 1)
    - Titles (Box 1)
      - A-C (Box 1)
      - D-F [Slide boxes 2-3] (Box 1)
      - G-L [Slide box 3] (Box 1)
      - R-U [Slide boxes 3-4] (Box 1)
  - Denmark (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous works [Slide box 4] (Box 1)
  - France (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous works (Box 1)
    - Titles (Box 1)
      - A-C (Box 1)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 1)
        - A Propos de Nice, 1931 (Box 1)
        - Ballet Mecanique, 1924 (Box 1)
        - Chien Andalou, 1928 (Box 1)
        - Colored Rhythmus [Slide boxes 4-5] (Box 1)
      - D-F [Slide box 5] (Box 1)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 1)
        - Emak Bakia, 1927 (Box 1)
        - La Folie de Dr. Tube, 1916 (Box 1)
      - G-L (Box 1)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 1)
        - L'Inhumaine, 1924 (Box 1)
      - M-Q (Box 1)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 1)
        - Menilmontant, 1924 [Slide box 6] (Box 1)
        - Napoleon, 1927 (Box 1)
        - Paris Qui Dort, 1923 (Box 1)
        - Passion of Joan of Arc, 1927 (Box 1)
        - Pecheur's d' Islande, 1924 (Box 1)
        - Pumpkin Race, 1907 (Box 1)
      - R-U (Box 1)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 1)
        - Retour a la Raison, 1923 (Box 1)
      - V-Z (Box 1)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 1)
        - Le Vertige, 1926 (Box 1)
        - Voyage to Moon, 1902 (Box 1)
  - Germany (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous works [Slide box 7] (Box 2)
    - Titles (Box 2)
      - A-C (Box 2)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 2)
        - Back Stairs, 1921 (Box 2)
        - Blue Angel, 1930 (Box 2)
        - The Cabinet of Dr. Caligari, 1920 [Slide boxes 7-8] (Box 2)
      - D-F [Slide box 8] (Box 2)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 2)
        - Destiny, 1921 (Box 2)
        - Four Devils, 1928 (Box 2)
      - G-K (Box 2)
        - Ghost before Breakfast, 1928 (Box 2)
        - Genuine, 1920 [Slide box 9] (Box 2)
        - Der Golem, 1920 (Box 2)
        - Joyless Street, 1925 (Box 2)
        - Kriemhild's Revenge, 1924 (Box 2)
      - L-N (Box 2)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 2)
        - Last Laugh, 1924 [Slide boxes 9-10] (Box 2)
        - Living Buddhas, 1924 [Slide Box 10] (Box 2)
        - Metropolis, 1926 (Box 2)
        - Die Nibelungen (Box 2)
        - Nosferatu, 1922 (Box 2)
      - O-R (Box 2)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 2)
        - Olympia, 1936 (Box 2)
        - Raskolnivok, 1924 (Box 2)
      - S-U (Box 2)
        - Miscellaneous works [Slide boxes 10-11] (Box 2)
        - Shattered (Le Rail), 1924 [Slide box 11] (Box 2)
        - Siegfried's Death, 1923 (Box 2)
        - The Street, 1923 (Box 2)
        - Sunrise, 1927 [Slide boxes 11-12] (Box 2)
        - Sylvester, 1923 [Slide box 12] (Box 2)
        - Tabu, 1931 (Box 2)
        - Torgus, 1921 (Box 2)
        - Triumph of the Will, 1934-36 (Box 2)
      - V-Z (Box 2)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 2)
        - Waxworks, 1924 (Box 2)
        - Way to Strength & Beauty, 1925 (Box 2)
        - Winnetou Series (Box 2)
  - Holland (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous works [Slide box 13] (Box 3)
  - Italy (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous works (Box 3)
    - Comparisons (Box 3)
    - Personalities (Box 3)
    - Posters (Box 3)
    - Spaghetti Westerns (Box 3)
    - Pasolini, Pier Paolo, 1922-1975 (Box 3)
    - Films Titles (Box 3)
      - A (Box 3)
      - B (Box 3)
      - C (Box 3)
      - D (Box 3)
      - E (Box 3)
      - F-G-H [Slide boxes 13-14] (Box 3)
      - I [Slide box 14] (Box 3)
      - L (Box 3)
      - M-N (Box 3)
      - O (Box 3)
      - P (Box 3)
      - Q-R (Box 3)
      - S (Box 3)
      - T (Box 3)
      - U (Box 3)
      - V (Box 3)
  - Russia (Box 3)
    General
    For Posters advertising Soviet Films, see Prints Russia: Lavinsky, Anton; Rodechencko, Alexandre, Stenberg, G&V. [Slide box 15]
    - Miscellaneous works (Box 3)
    - Titles (Box 3)
      - A-G (Box 3)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 3)
        - Alexander Nevsky, 1938 (Box 3)
        - Arsenal, 1928 (Box 3)
        - By the Law, 1926 (Box 3)
        - Deserter, 1934 (Box 3)
        - Earth, 1930 (Box 3)
        - End of St. Petersburg, 1927 (Box 3)
      - H-M (Box 3)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 3)
        - Ivan the Terrible, 1944 (Box 3)
        - Man with a Movie Camera, 1929 (Box 3)
        - Mother, 1926 [Slide box 16] (Box 3)
      - N-R (Box 3)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 3)
        - October, 1927 (Box 3)
        - Old & New, 1929 (Box 3)
        - Potemkin, 1925 (Box 3)
          Xx for Poster designed by Rodchencko, see Prints Russia
      - S-Z (Box 3)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 3)
        - Strike, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Sweden [Slide box 17] (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous works (Box 3)
    - Korkarlen, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Switzerland (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous works (Box 3)
  - United States (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous works (Box 3)
    - Personalities (Box 3)
    - Films Makers (Box 3)
      - Berkeley, Busby, 1895 (Box 3)
      - Chaplin, Charlie, 1825-1891 (Box 3)
        Also by Title: The Tramp and A Woman of Paris
      - Disney, Walt (Box 3)
      - Griffith, D.W. [Slide box 18] (Box 3)
      - Laurel & Hardy (Box 3)
      - Nauman, Bruce, 1941 (Box 3)
      - Pixar Animation Studios (Box 3)
      - Sennett, Mack (Box 3)
      - Sternberg, Josef von (Box 3)
      - Trinh, T. Minh-Ha, 1952- (Box 3)
      - Warhol, Andy (Box 3)
        See also Painting U.S. & Prints U.S.
    - Titles (Box 3)
      - A (Box 3)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 3)
        - Abraham Lincoln, 1930 (Box 3)
        - America, 1924 (Box 3)
        - An America Tragedy, 1931 (Box 3)
      - B (Box 3)
        - Miscellaneous works [Slide boxes 18-19] (Box 3–4)
        - Battle of the Sexes, 1928 [Slide box 19] (Box 4)
        - Blade Runner, 1982 (Box 4)
        - Blonde Venus, 1932 (Box 4)
        - Broken Blossoms, 1919 (Box 4)
        - Bronco Billy (Box 4)
      - C (Box 4)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 4)
        - Case of Lena Smith, 1929 (Box 4)
        - The Cat & The Canary, 1927 (Box 4)
        - Chip of the Flying U, 1914 (Box 4)
        - Citizen Kane, 1940 [Slide box 20] (Box 4)
        - Cleopatra (all versions) (Box 4)
        - Corner in Wheat, 1909 (Box 4)
        - The covered Wagon, 1923 (Box 4)
        - Crime & Punishment, 1935 (Box 4)
        - Cupid's Day Off, 1918 (Box 4)
      - D (Box 4)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 4)
        - Desert Gold, 1920 (Box 4)
        - Devil is a Woman, 1930 (Box 4)
        - Dishonored, 1931 (Box 4)
        - Docks of New York, 1929 (Box 4)
        - Dr. Jekyil & Mr. Hyde, 1920 (Box 4)
        - Down on the Farm, 1920 (Box 4)
        - Drag Net, 1928 (Box 4)
        - Dream Street, 1921 [Slide box 21] (Box 4)
      - E (Box 4)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 4)
        - Exquisite Sinner, 1925 (Box 4)
      - F (Box 4)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 4)
        - Forty-Second Street, 1933 (Box 4)
        - Fountainhead, 1949 (Box 4)
        - Frankenstein, 1931 (Box 4)
      - G (Box 4)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 4)
        - The General, 1928 (Box 4)
        - Girl of the Golden West, 1923 (Box 4)
        - Golddiggers of 1933 (Box 4)
        - Golddiggers of 1935 (Box 4)
        - The Great love, 1918 (Box 4)
        - Greatest Thing in Life, 1918 (Box 4)
      - H (Box 4)
        - Miscellaneous works [Slide boxes 21-22] (Box 4)
        - The Haunted Hotel, 1902 [Slide box 22] (Box 4)
        - High Moon, 1952 (Box 4)
      - I (Box 4)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 4)
        - Intolerance, 1916 (Box 4)
          - Babylonian Story (Box 4)
          - Story of Christ [Slide boxes 22-23] (Box 4)
          - Huguenot Story [Slide box 23] (Box 4)
          - Modern Story (Box 4)
        - Isn't Life Wonderful, 1925 (Box 4)
      - J (Box 4)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 4)
      - K (Box 4)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 4)
      - L (Box 4)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 4)
        - Last Command, 1928 (Box 4)
        - Louisiana Story, 1946 (Box 4)
      - M (Box 4)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 4)
        - The Marriage Circle, 1924 (Box 4)
        - Meet Me In St. Louis, 1944 [Slide box 24] (Box 4)
        - Moana, 1923-1924 (Box 4)
        - Morocco, 1930 (Box 4)
        - Murders on Rue Morgue, 1932 (Box 4)
      - N (Box 4)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 4)
        - Nanouk of the North, 1921 (Box 4)
        - Navigator (Box 4)
        - New York Hat (Box 4)
      - O (Box 4)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 4)
        - Orphans of the Storm, 1921 (Box 4)
      - P (Box 4)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 4)
      - Q (Box 4)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 4)
      - S (Box 4)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 4)
        - Sally of the Sawdust, 1925 [Slide box 25] (Box 5)
        - Scarlet Days, 1919 (Box 5)
        - Shangai Express, 1934 (Box 5)
        - Shangai Gesture, 1941 (Box 5)
        - Small Town Idol, 1921 (Box 5)
        - Sorrows of Satan, 1926 (Box 5)
        - The Spoilers, 1923 (Box 5)
        - The Squaw Man (Box 5)
      - T (Box 5)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 5)
        - Ten Commandments, 1914 and 1956 (Box 5)
        - Three Badmen & a Girl, 1914 (Box 5)
        - Thunderbolt, 1929 (Box 5)
        - The Tramp, 1915 [Slide box 26] (Box 5)
        - True Heart Susie, 1919 (Box 5)
      - U-V (Box 5)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 5)
        - Underworld, 1927 (Box 5)
        - The Virginian, 1914 (Box 5)
      - W (Box 5)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 5)
        - Way Down East, 1920 (Box 5)
        - The White Rose, 1923 (Box 5)
        - Williamson Submarine Expedition, 1914 (Box 5)
        - Wizard of Oz, 1938 (Box 5)
        - A woman of Paris, 1928 (Box 5)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 5)
        - Miscellaneous works (Box 5)
- Photography (Box 5)
  - General [Slide box 27] (Box 5)
    Xx Film History: for other types of cameras, magic lanterns, moving toys
    - Anthropology (Box 5)
    - Camera Lucida- Camera Obscura (Box 5)
    - Cameras & Equipment (Box 5)
    - Early Photography, Near East (Box 5)
      Xx Frith, Robert (Britain) and Ducamp, Maxime (France)
    - Exhibitions (Box 5)
      - Film & Foto, Werkbund 1929 (Box 5)
      - Harlem on my Mind, 1978 (Box 5)
      - MOMA (Box 5)
        - Various Exhibitions (Box 5)
        - Family of Man (Box 5)
      - Feminism [Slide boxes 27-28] (Box 5)
      - History [Slide box 28] (Box 5)
      - Jews in Europe (Box 5)
        Xx Painting Germany 20th century for exhibits of "degenerate art"
      - Medicine (Box 5)
      - Photo Icons (Box 5)
        Xx Doisneau (France), Eisenstadt (U.S.) for kissing couples
      - Science (Box 5)
      - Space (Box 5)
      - Techniques (Box 5)
      - Taxonomy (Box 5)
      - War [Slide box 29] (Box 5)
        Xx Photography U.S.-Barnard, George and Gardner, Alexander
        - American Civil (Box 5)
          Xx for additional photos –Gardner, Alexander and O'Sullivan, T.H.
        - WW I (Box 5)
          Xx War World I
        - WW II (Box 5)
          Xx War World II
  - Australia (Box 5)
    - Lindt, John W., 1845-1926 (Box 5)
  - Austria (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous Artists (Box 5)
    - Mayer, Dr. Emil, 1871-1938 (Box 5)
  - Belgium (Box 5)
    - Magritte, Rene, 1898-1967 (Box 5)
  - Brazil (Box 5)
    - Salgado, Sebastien, 1944- [Slide box 30] (Box 5)
  - Britain (Box 5)
    - Unknown Artists (Box 5)
      - Hannah Cullwick Photographs (Box 5)
    - Known Artists (Box 5)
      - Annan, J. Craig, 1864-1946 (Box 5)
      - Annan, Thomas, 1830-1888 (Box 5)
      - Atkins, Anna, 1799-1871 (Box 5)
      - Atkinson, Conrad, 1940- (Box 5)
      - Auden, W.H., 1907-1973 (Box 5)
      - Beato, Felice Antonio, ca.1825-ca.1907 (Box 5)
      - Beato, Felice Antonio, ca.1825-ca.1907 (Box 5)
      - Bedford, Francis, 1816-1894 (Box 5)
      - Billingham, Richard, 1970- (Box 5)
      - Bourne, Samuel, 1834-1912 [Slide boxes 30-31] (Box 5–6)
      - Brandt, Bill, 1906- [Slide box 31] (Box 6)
      - Bridges, Reverand (Box 6)
      - Burgin, Victor, 1941- (Box 6)
      - Cameron, Julia Margaret, 1815-1879 [Slide boxes 31-32] (Box 6)
      - Carroll, Lewis, 1832-1898 [Slide box 32] (Box 6)
      - Cooper, Michael, 1941-1978 (Box 6)
      - Coster, Howard (Box 6)
      - Curry, F.C., Ca.1860's (Box 6)
      - Davison, George, 1856-1930 (Box 6)
      - Delamotte, Philip Henry, 1820-1889 (Box 6)
      - Diamond, Hugh Welch, 1809-1866 (Box 6)
      - Dickens, C.S.S. (Box 6)
      - Dugmore, Arthur R., 1870-1955 (Box 6)
      - Emerson, Peter, 1856-1936 (Box 6)
      - Evans, Frederick Henry, 1853-1943 (Box 6)
      - Fani-Kayode, Rotimi, 1955-1989 (Box 6)
      - Fenton, Roger, 1819-1869 (Box 6)
      - Floyd, William Pryor (Box 6)
      - Frith, Francis, 1822-1899 (Box 6)
      - Fulton, Hamish, 1946- (Box 6)
      - Garratt, Colin, ca.1969 (Box 6)
      - Gillick, Liam, 1964- (Box 6)
      - Green, William, 1934- (Box 6)
      - Grenfell, Katya (Box 6)
      - Hamilton, Richard1922- (Box 6)
      - Hawarden, Lady Clemetina, 1822-1865 (Box 6)
      - Hill, D.O. & Adamson, R. (Box 6)
      - Hilliard, John, 1954- (Box 6)
      - Hockney, David, 1937- [Slide box 33] (Box 6)
      - Hooper, Willoughby W., 1837-1912 (Box 6)
      - Howlett, Robert, 1831-1858 (Box 6)
      - Hylton, Richard, 1967- (Box 6)
      - Jones, Calvert R., 1802-1877 (Box 6)
      - Keith, Thomas, 1827-1895 (Box 6)
      - Llewellyn, John D. (Box 6)
      - London, Jack, 1876-1916 (Box 6)
      - Lyon, Edmund David, ca.1829-1891 (Box 6)
      - Martin, Paul, 1864-1944 (Box 6)
      - McCartney, Linda, 1941-1998 (Box 6)
      - McLean, Bruce, 1942- (Box 6)
      - Mayall, John E., 1810-1901 (Box 6)
      - Merlin, Henry B., 1830-1873 (Box 6)
      - Moreley, Lewis, 1925- (Box 6)
      - Murray, John, 1809-1898 (Box 6)
      - Muybridge, Eadweard, 1830-1904 (Box 6)
      - Nasmyth, James, 1808-1890 (Box 6)
      - Park, Bertram, 1883-1972 (Box 6)
      - Rejlander, Oscar Gustave, 1813-1875 (Box 6)
      - Robertson, James D., ca.1855-1870 (Box 6)
      - Robinson, Henry, 1830-1901 (Box 6)
      - Shepherd, Charles, ca.1853 (Box 6)
      - Spender, John H., 1910- (Box 6)
      - Sutcliffe, Frank Meadow, 1853-1941 (Box 6)
      - Talbot, William Henry Fox., 1800-1877 (Box 6)
      - Tanquereay, Paul (Box 6)
      - Thomson, John, 1837-1921 [Slide box 34] (Box 6)
      - Tripe, Linnaeus, 1822-1902 (Box 6)
      - Waterhouse, James, 1842-1922 (Box 6)
      - Webb, Boyd, 1947- (Box 6)
      - White, Henry, 1819-1903 (Box 6)
      - Yates, Marie (Box 6)
  - Canada (Box 6)
    - Various artists (Box 6)
    - Cadieux, Genevieve, 1955- (Box 6)
    - Notman, William, 1826-1891 (Box 6)
    - Karsh, Yousuf, 1908- (Box 6)
  - Cuba (Box 6)
    - Mendieta, Ana, 1948-1985 (Box 6)
  - Czechoslovakia [Slide box 35] (Box 6)
    - Various Artists (Box 6)
  - France (Box 6)
    - Anonymous & Miscellaneous Artists (Box 6)
    - Alibert (Box 6)
    - Appert, Eugene, act.1871- (Box 6)
    - Atget, Eugene, 1857-1927 (Box 6)
      - Undated Photos (1900-1925) (Box 6)
      - Dated Photos (Box 6)
        - 1900-1909 (Box 6)
        - 1910-1919 (Box 6)
        - 1920-1927 (Box 6)
      - Aubry, Charles [Slide box 36] (Box 6)
      - Bachard, H., act.1870-act.1880 (Box 6)
      - Baldus, Edouard, 1820- (Box 6)
      - Bayard, Hippolyte, 1801-1887 (Box 6)
      - Bisson Brothers (Box 6)
      - Blanquart-Evrard (Box 6)
      - Bioffard, J.A., 1902-1961 (Box 6)
      - Brassai, 1899-1984 (Box 6)
      - Braun, Adolphe (Box 6)
        Xx Countess Castiglione—Other Photographs of her see under Pierson, Louis
      - Cahun, Claude, 1894-1954 [Slide box 37] (Box 7)
      - Calle, Sophie, 1953- (Box 7)
      - Carjat, Etienne, 1828-1906 (Box 7)
      - Cartier-Bresson, Henri, 1908- (Box 7)
      - Castiglione (Box 7)
        Xx for photographs of Countess Castiglione, see under Braun, Adolphe and Pierson, Louis
      - Charcot, Jean Martin, 1825-1893 (Box 7)
      - Charnay Désiré, 1828-1915 (Box 7)
      - Claudet, A. F.J., 1797-1867 (Box 7)
      - Clausel, Alexandre J.P., 1802-1884 (Box 7)
      - Clerambault, Gaetan de, 1872-1934 (Box 7)
      - Couppier, Jules, 19th century (Box 7)
      - Daguerre, Louis Jacques Mande, 1781-1851 (Box 7)
        Xx for diorama – Film History- Panorama; for Inauguration of Solomon's Temple, by Daguerre- under Painting France Daguerre
      - Davane, Louis A., 1824-1912 (Box 7)
      - Degas, Edgar, 1843-1917 (Box 7)
      - Demachy, Robert, 1859-1937 (Box 7)
      - Disderi, Andre, 1819-1890 (Box 7)
      - Doisneau, Robert, 1912- (Box 7)
      - Drahos, Tom (Box 7)
      - Ducamp, Maxine, 1822-1894 (Box 7)
      - Duchenne de Boulogne, 1806-1875 [Slide box 38] (Box 7)
      - Ducos-Du-Hauron, L., 1837-1920 (Box 7)
      - Durieu, Eugene, 1800-1874 (Box 7)
      - Faucon, Bernard, 1950- (Box 7)
      - Ferrier, C. (Box 7)
      - Fizeau, H.L., 1819-1896 (Box 7)
      - Fleischer, Alain, 1944- (Box 7)
      - Freund, Gisele, 1913-1974 (Box 7)
      - Garnell, Jean-Louis, 1964- (Box 7)
      - Gid, Raymond, 1905- (Box 7)
      - Gros, Jean Baptiste Louis., 1790-1870 (Box 7)
      - Hugo, C. (Box 7)
      - Hugnet, Georges, 1906-1974 (Box 7)
      - Jouvin, Hippolyte (Box 7)
      - Kern, Pascal (Box 7)
      - Kollar, Francois, 1904-1979 (Box 7)
      - Landau, Ergy (Box 7)
      - Langlois, Charles, 1789-1870 (Box 7)
      - Lartigue, Henri, 1896- (Box 7)
      - Legrange, Alexis de, 1825- ? (Box 7)
      - Le Gray, Gustave, 1820-1886 (Box 7)
      - Lerebours, Noel-Marie-Paymal, 1807-1873 (Box 7)
      - Le Secq, Henri, 1818-1882 (Box 7)
      - Lotar, Eli, 1905-ca.1970 (Box 7)
      - Lumiere, Louis (Box 7)
      - Luys, Jules (Dr.) (Box 7)
      - Maar, Dora, 1909- (Box 7)
      - Marconi, Guglielmo, ca.1869-1874 (Box 7)
      - Marey, Etienne-Jules, 1830-1904 [Slide boxes 38-39] (Box 7)
      - Marville, Charles, 1816-ca.1879 [Slide box 39] (Box 7)
      - Nadar, Gaspar Felix,1820-1910 (Box 7)
        Xx for Nadar's photograph of Edouard Manet- Painting France- Manet, Edouard photographs
      - Nadar, Paul, 1856-1939 (Box 7)
      - Negre, Charles, 1820-1880 [Slide box 40] (Box 7)
      - Niepce, Joseph Nicephore, 1765-1833 (Box 7)
      - Parry, Roger, 1905-1977 (Box 7)
      - Pedra, Joseph, act.c.1860- (Box 7)
      - Peress, Gilles (Box 7)
      - Pierson, Louis (Box 7)
      - Puyo, Constant, 1857-1933 (Box 7)
      - Regnault, Felix Louis (Box 7)
      - Regnault, Henri, 1810-1878 (Box 7)
      - Riboud, Marc, 1923- (Box 7)
      - Robert, Louis-Remy, 1811-1882 (Box 7)
      - Rondin, Hector (Box 7)
      - Rousse, Georges, 1947- (Box 7)
      - Seeberger, J., L. & H. (Box 7)
      - Sougez, Emmanuel, 1889-1972 (Box 7)
      - Tabard, Maurice, 1897-1984 (Box 7)
      - Taupenot, J.M., 1824-1856 (Box 7)
      - Thibault, Eugene [Slide box 41] (Box 7)
      - Tosani, Patrick, 1954- (Box 7)
      - Ubac, Raoul, 1910-1985 (Box 7)
      - Vallou de Villeneuve, 1795-1866 (Box 7)
      - Voland, Henri, ca.. Before 1857-77 (Box 7)
      - Von Martens, Friedrich (Box 7)
      - Vuillard, Edouard, 1868-1940 (Box 7)
      - Zola, Emile, 1840-1902 (Box 7)
  - Germany (Box 7)
    - Unknown Artists (Box 7)
      - Bauhaus Photography (Box 7)
      - Nazi Photography (Box 7)
    - Known Artists (Box 7)
      - Aichinger, Franz (Box 7)
      - Baumgarten, Lothar, 1949- (Box 7)
      - Bayer, Herbert, 1900-1986 (Box 7)
      - Becher, Bernd & Hilla, act. 1959- (Box 7)
      - Bellmer, Hans, 1902-1975 [Slide box 42] (Box 7)
      - Bertolf, Hans (Box 7)
      - Bing, Ilse, 1899-1988 (Box 7)
      - Biow, Herman, 1810-1850 (Box 7)
      - Blossfeldt, Karl, 1865-1932 (Box 7)
      - Blumenfeld, Erwin, 1897-1969 (Box 7)
      - Both, Katt (Box 7)
      - Brandt, Marianne, 1893-1983 (Box 7)
      - Burchartz, Max, 1887-1961 (Box 7)
      - Comeriner, Erich, 1907-1978 (Box 7)
      - Finsler, Hans, 1891-1972 (Box 7)
      - Flatz, Wolfgang, 1952- (Box 7)
      - Forg, Gunther, 1952- (Box 7)
      - Gloeden, Wilhelm von 1856-1931 (Box 7)
      - Gorny, Hein, 1904-1969 (Box 7)
      - Gropius, Walter, 1883-1969 (Box 7)
      - Gursky, Andreas, 1955- (Box 7)
      - Haeckel Brothers, act.c.1914- (Box 7)
      - Heartfield, John, 1891-1968 (Box 7)
      - Herz, Rudolf, 1954- (Box 7)
      - Hoffman, Heinrich, 1885-1957 (Box 7)
      - Hutte, Axel (Box 7)
      - Junger, Ernst [Slide box 43] (Box 8)
      - Lehndorff & Trulzsch (Box 8)
      - Lex-Nerlinger, Alice (Box 8)
      - Man, Felix H., 1893-1985 (Box 8)
      - Mantz, Werner, 1901- (Box 8)
      - Meyer, Hannes, 1889-1954 (Box 8)
      - Moholy, Lucia, 1899- (Box 8)
      - Mucha, Reinhard (Box 8)
      - Newton, Helmut, 1920- (Box 8)
      - Peterhans, Walter, 1897-1960 (Box 8)
      - Renger-Patzsch, Albert, 1897-1966 (Box 8)
      - Riefenstahl, Leni, 1902- (Box 8)
      - Ringl + Pit, 1929 (Box 8)
        X Ringl + Pit(Grete Stern & Ellen Auerbach)
        X Ringl + Pit (G. Stern & E. Auerbach)
      - Roehr, Peter, 1944-1988 (Box 8)
      - Ruff, Thomas, 1958- [Slide boxes 43-44] (Box 8)
      - Rudolph, Charlotte, act.c.1925- [Slide box 44] (Box 8)
      - Salomon, Erich, 1886-1944 (Box 8)
      - Sander, August 1876-1964 (Box 8)
      - Schad, Christian, 1894-1982 [Slide box 45] (Box 8)
      - Schillings, Carl Georg, 1865-1921 (Box 8)
      - Schleifer, Fritz (Box 8)
      - Schurmann, Herbert (Box 8)
      - Sebald, W.G., 1944-2001 (Box 8)
      - Seidenstucker, Friedrich, 1882-1966 (Box 8)
      - Sesse, Jorg, 1962- (Box 8)
      - Sieverding, Katharine, 1944- (Box 8)
      - Steffen, Wilhelm, act.c.1919- (Box 8)
      - Steinert, Otto, 1915- (Box 8)
      - Stelzner, Carl F., 1805-1894 (Box 8)
      - Struth, Thomas, 1954- (Box 8)
      - Sudek, Josef, 1896-1976 (Box 8)
      - Tillmans, Wolfgang, 1968- (Box 8)
      - Tschichold, Jan, 1902-1976 (Box 8)
        Xx Photography General- Exhibitions-
      - Umbo, 1902-1980 (Box 8)
      - Wols, Alfred Otto Wolfgang, 1913-1959 (Box 8)
  - Holland (Box 8)
    - Lamsweerde, Inez van 1963- (Box 8)
    - Polak, Richard, 1870-1957 (Box 8)
    - Zwart, Piet, 1885-1977 (Box 8)
  - Hungary [Slide Box 46] (Box 8)
    - Moholy-Nagy, Laszlo, 1895-1946 (Box 8)
    - Munkacsi, Martin, 1896-1963 (Box 8)
    - Muray, Nicholas, 1892-1965 (Box 8)
  - India (Box 8)
    - Various Artists (Box 8)
  - Israel (Box 8)
    - Various Artists (Box 8)
  - Italy (Box 8)
    - Various Artists (Box 8)
      X for Bisi, Gianetto –Painting Italy- Boccioni, Umberto, General
    - Bragaglia, Anton G., 1890-1960 (Box 8)
    - Wulz, Wanda, 1903-1984 (Box 8)
  - Luxembourg (Box 8)